bizbash.com 2016-11-23

# Privacy Policy

yipee! an advertisement

Welcome to www.BizBash.com (the “Website”). This website is owned and operated by BizBash Media, Inc. ( **“we”, “us”, “our”** ). We are committed to protecting your privacy. This policy provides you with details on the information we collect from you and the uses we make of your personal information. If you do not want us accessing and/or using your personal information as described herein, please do not provide us with any! **This policy may be updated from time to time without prior notice, so please check back periodically. If you continue to visit this Website and use the services made available to you after such changes have been made, you hereby provide your consent to the changes.**

We encourage you to read this policy to learn more about what information of yours we collect and how we use it and how you can “opt-out” of receiving communications from us. Additionally, this policy includes information about how we endeavor to protect your data. If you have any questions about our collection and use of your information, please contact us at [info@bizbash.com.](mailto:info@bizbash.com)

  1. **Information Collected; Use of Information; Sharing of Information**
    1. **Personally Identifiable Information**   
If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence. We may collect personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) such as your name, address, telephone number, date of birth and e-mail address from you. Personal Information is collected via voluntary submissions from you. If you do not want to provide us with your Personal Information, you may still access the Website but certain areas may not be accessible to you. If you choose to submit content to any public area of the Website, your content will be considered “public” and will not be subject to the privacy protections set forth herein or any applicable law, rule or regulation. We encourage you to exercise caution when making decisions about what information you disclose in such public areas. Furthermore, except as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy, any content you post to a public area of the Website may be used by us for any purpose.

Your Personal Information may be used by us (i) to process your registration requests, purchase orders and promotions entries; (ii) communicate with you; (iii) administer assistance to you when requested; and (iv) as required by applicable laws, rules or regulations, or the Terms of Use applicable to this Website. We may share your Personal Information with third parties to further the purpose for which you provided such information to us, for example, in order to process a purchase order. We also share your Personal Information with third parties if we believe that the law requires us to do, or to protect our own property or the property of our affiliates. Additionally, in the event of a corporate restructuring (such as, a sale, merger or other asset transfer), we may share your Personal Information with a third party.

    2. **Non-Personally Identifiable Information**   

Certain non-personally identifiable information (“Non-Personal Information”) about our visitors is collected by the standard operation of our Internet servers and through the use of “cookies”. A “cookie” is a small amount of data sent to your browser from a web server and stored by your computer. Generally, cookies are used to enable us to deliver to you a better and more personalized service, assist us in tracking visits to the Website and to measure visitor patterns. This information is not personally identifiable and is used by us only to improve the Website. We do not use cookies to retrieve Personal Information from your computer, or use cookies to retrieve other information from your computer for purposes that are unrelated to the Website or your interaction with the Website. We reserve the right to disclose or utilize any of this information in aggregate form, for any purpose, in our sole judgment. The Non-Personal Information we collect is used by us to improve the content of our Website and enhance your experience. Third party advertisers that serve ads on the Website may also use their own cookies. By modifying your browser preferences, you can accept or reject all cookies. If you choose to reject all cookies, you will not be able to access the portions of the Website that require you to register in order to participate. 

You may have certain rights under the Communications Act, Federal Trade Commission Act, and other state and federal statutes that may apply, and by accepting these terms and using the Website, you are waiving all of these rights as to collection, use, disclosure and storage of your Personal Information and Non-Personal Information collected by us.

  2. **Protection for Children and Minors.**

**This Website is not intended for, and we have no intention of collecting personally identifiable information from persons under the age of 18.** If a person under the age of 18 has provided us with personally identifiable information, we will use all reasonable efforts to delete such information from our database. If you are under the age of 18, you are not authorized to access or submit any content or information to this Website. 

  3. **Opt-Out.**

If you do not want to receive email or other communications from us in the future, please send an email to us at the address below or call us at the telephone number below requesting to be removed from our mailing list. You will also have the option of clicking on a link included in email correspondence you receive from us in order to remove yourself from our mailing list. 

> Email Contact: remove@bizbash.com  
>  Telephone Contact: 646.839.6835 

Please note that there might be a brief delay between when you submit your request to “opt-out” and when it is processed and reflected in our systems; accordingly you may continue to receive communications from us for a limited time after you unsubscribe. We appreciate your patience.

  4. **Security.**

We are committed to using commercially reasonable efforts to maintaining the security of your Personal Information. To help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we adhere to industry standard practices and procedures to help safeguard and secure the information we collect. Although we use commercially reasonable efforts to protect the security of your Personal Information and our system, due to the inherent open nature of the Internet, no transmission via the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result of this and other factors beyond our control, we cannot guarantee the security of the information that you transmit to or through our Website. Therefore, you assume that risk by using the Website.

  5. **Security.**

This Website contains links to other websites for the purchase of third party products and services. Please be aware that we are not responsible for such third party sites in any manner including without limitation, the privacy practices of other websites. We encourage you to be aware when you access any such third party links and to read the privacy policies of each website that you access. This Privacy Policy only applies to information collected by us by this Website.

  6. **Links to Other Websites.**

This Website contains links to other websites for the purchase of third party products and services. Please be aware that we are not responsible for such third party sites in any manner including without limitation, the privacy practices of other websites. We encourage you to be aware when you access any such third party links and to read the privacy policies of each website that you access. This Privacy Policy only applies to information collected by us by this Website.

  7. **Offers and Promotions.**

We may from time to time offer you opportunities that are sponsored or co-branded with third parties. Such content may include contests, sweepstakes or promotions. In connection with such opportunities, the relevant third parties may obtain Personal Information that you voluntarily submit to participate in such opportunity. We have no control over these third parties’ use of such information.

  8. **Contact Us.**

If you have any questions, comments or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy and/or the practices described herein, please email us at [info@bizbash.com](mailto:info@bizbash.com) or write us at **115 W 27th Street, Floor 8, New York, NY 10001.**

  9. **Governing Law.**

This Privacy Policy and our legal obligations hereunder are subject to the laws of New York, U.S.A., regardless of your location. You hereby consent to the exclusive jurisdiction of and venue in the federal and state courts located in New York County, New York, U.S.A. in all disputes arising out of or relating to the Services. 

**Your use of this Website is governed by, and subject to, the legal notices and disclaimers located at http://www.bizbash.com/termsandconditions is subject at all times to all such legal notices and disclaimers. Furthermore, your use and access of the Website constitutes your agreement to be bound by the provisions contained in the Terms of Use and in this Privacy Policy.**

This Privacy Policy was last updated on March 1st, 2012. 

Your email inquiry will be sent to 3 venue

[[DYNAMIC INTERSTITIAL]]
